University of Arizona Agricultural Experiment Station annual reports, 1919-1961
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
University of Arizona Agricultural Experiment Station annual reports, 1919-1961
AZ 529
University of Arizona. Agricultural Experiment Station
Typescript reports on crops, weather, and horticulture. Some include photographs and financial statements.
2.8 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Scope and Content Note
Typescript reports on crops, weather, and horticulture. Some include photographs and financial statements.
University of Arizona -- History; University of Arizona. Agricultural Experiment Station -- Records and correspondence; Agriculture -- Arizona; Agriculture -- Arizona -- Mesa; Agriculture -- Arizona -- Prescott; Agriculture -- Arizona -- Safford; Agriculture -- Arizona -- Salt River Valley; Agriculture -- Arizona -- Sulphur Springs Valley; Agriculture -- Arizona -- Tempe; Agriculture -- Arizona -- Yuma County; Horticulture -- Arizona; Irrigation -- Arizona; Soils -- Arizona; Agricultural experiment stations -- Arizona; Records; Correspondence; Photographs
Container List
- Mesa Agricultural Experiment Station. Annual Reports. 1952, 1953, 1955, 1956 (Box 1)
- Prescott Dry Farm. Annual Reports. 1916-1927 (Box 1A)
- Stafford Experimental Farm. Specifications for House, Carport, and Office Hay Shed, Seed Storage and Machine Shed. 1946 (Box 2)
- Stafford Experiment Farm. Annual Reports. 1951, 1956, 1957 (Box 2)
- Salt River Valley Farm. Annual Reports. 1936, 1938, 1940, 1946 (Box 2)
- Salt River Valley Farm. Annual Reports. 1947-1951 (Box 3)
- Sulphur Springs Valley Experiment Farm. Annual Reports. 1919-1923 (Box 4)
- Tempe Citrus Experiment Station. Annual Reports. 1950-1952 (Box 4)
- Tempe Cotton Research Farm. Annual Reports. 1956-1957 (Box 5)
- (Tempe) U.S. Water Conservation Laboratory. Annual Reports. 1961 (Box 5)
- Yuma Mesa Soil and Crop Laboratory. Annual Reports. 1952, 1954 (Box 5)
- Yuma Mesa Experiment Station. Reports. 1953-1957, 1961 (Box 6)
- Yuma Farms. Reports. 1948-1952 (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 7)